# ANITHA N

### WEB DEVELOPER

- 88928-23783
- ✓ anitha.nagadasarik95@gmail.com
- Banglore, Karnataka
- https://github.com/anithanagadasarink

# SKILLS

- Web Tech: HTML, CSS, Javascript
- CSS Fremeworks: Tailwind, Bootstrap, SASS
- Control Versions: Git, Github
- CMS: Sitecore and Wordpress
- Design tools: Photoshop, Adobe XD
- · Problem-Solving
- Project Management Tools
- Good Communication
- Self-Disciplined and motivated

## EDUCATION

## BACHELOR OF COMPUTER APPLICATION

Banglore University

2014 - 2017: 80.5%

#### SECONDARY EDUCATION

Pre-University Colloge Board

2012 - 2014: 86.5%

## **PROFILE**

I'm a qualified and professional web developer with five years of experience in designing, developing, and managing complex websites and internal frameworks. Specalise in HTML, CSS, Javascript, and responsive design. Translated of the UI/UX design wireframes to actual code that to produce visual elements of the application.

## EXPERIENCE

### WEB DEVLOPER

Indegene Pvt. Ltd.

2020 - Present

- · Converted PSD to websites with pixel perfect
- Worked on 6+ Sitecore projects
- Worked on .net projects and maintenance projects

#### WEB DESIGNER

Odysseus Solutions Pvt. Ltd

2018-2019

- Worked as Web Developer. Involved in Developing and designing of web applications.
- Implemented new features and extended existing functionality to the web page.

#### UI DEVELOPER

Floret Media Pvt. Ltd

2017 - 2018

- Worked on 15+ projects from scratch
- Worked on Wordpress projects
- Handled UAE clients